[
    {
        "question": "Father",
        "choice1": "el padre",
        "choice2": "el hijo",
        "choice3": "la familia cercana",
        "choice4": "la hermana",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Dad",
        "choice1": "el hermano",
        "choice2": "el hijo",
        "choice3": "la hija",
        "choice4": "el papá",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Mother",
        "choice1": "el padre",
        "choice2": "la hija",
        "choice3": "la madre",
        "choice4": "el hermano",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Mum",
        "choice1": "el hijo",
        "choice2": "la mamá",
        "choice3": "el papá",
        "choice4": "la hija",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Brother",
        "choice1": "la mamá",
        "choice2": "el hermano",
        "choice3": "el padre",
        "choice4": "el hijo",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Sister",
        "choice1": "el hermano",
        "choice2": "la mamá",
        "choice3": "la hermana",
        "choice4": "el papá",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Son",
        "choice1": "el hijo",
        "choice2": "el papá",
        "choice3": "la hermana",
        "choice4": "la mamá",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Daughter",
        "choice1": "la hija",
        "choice2": "el papá",
        "choice3": "la mamá",
        "choice4": "el padre",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Close Family",
        "choice1": "la hermana",
        "choice2": "el hermano",
        "choice3": "la hija",
        "choice4": "la familia cercana",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Grandfather",
        "choice1": "el abuelo",
        "choice2": "la abuela",
        "choice3": "el tío",
        "choice4": "la nieta",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Grandmother",
        "choice1": "el nieto",
        "choice2": "la bisabuela",
        "choice3": "la abuela",
        "choice4": "el abuelo",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Great-Grandfather",
        "choice1": "la nieta",
        "choice2": "el bisabuelo",
        "choice3": "el abuelo",
        "choice4": "el tío",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Great-Grandmother",
        "choice1": "la nieta",
        "choice2": "el tío",
        "choice3": "el nieto",
        "choice4": "la bisabuela",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Granddaughter",
        "choice1": "la nieta",
        "choice2": "el abuelo",
        "choice3": "el tío",
        "choice4": "el bisabuelo",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Grandson",
        "choice1": "el bisabuelo",
        "choice2": "la bisabuela",
        "choice3": "la nieta",
        "choice4": "el nieto",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Uncle",
        "choice1": "mis parientes",
        "choice2": "la bisabuela",
        "choice3": "el tío",
        "choice4": "el bisabuelo",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Aunt",
        "choice1": "el bisabuelo",
        "choice2": "la tía",
        "choice3": "el nieto",
        "choice4": "el tío abuelo",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Great-Uncle",
        "choice1": "el tío abuelo",
        "choice2": "el bisabuelo",
        "choice3": "mis parientes",
        "choice4": "la prima",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Great-Aunt",
        "choice1": "la bisabuela",
        "choice2": "el primo",
        "choice3": "la abuela",
        "choice4": "la tía abuela",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Cousin (Male)",
        "choice1": "el primo",
        "choice2": "la prima",
        "choice3": "el bisabuelo",
        "choice4": "el tío abuelo",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Cousin (Female)",
        "choice1": "la abuela",
        "choice2": "la prima",
        "choice3": "el tío abuelo",
        "choice4": "la nieta",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "My Relatives",
        "choice1": "la prima",
        "choice2": "la abuela",
        "choice3": "mis parientes",
        "choice4": "el primo",
        "answer": 3
    }
]